<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What we offer on ITology s.r.o.</title>
    <link>https://jirimar.github.io/products/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What we offer on ITology s.r.o.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jirimar.github.io/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Business analysis</title>
      <link>https://jirimar.github.io/products/analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jirimar.github.io/products/analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We offer comprehensive services in business analysis to help organizations clearly define their needs and transform them into effective, feasible IT solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our business analysts work closely with stakeholders to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Identify and refine business requirements&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Evaluate the current state and define the future vision&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Estimate implementation costs and assess project impacts&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Provide time and resource estimates&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prepare detailed functional and technical designs (detail design)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Collaborate with development and QA teams during implementation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Warehousing</title>
      <link>https://jirimar.github.io/products/dwh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jirimar.github.io/products/dwh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At ITology, we specialize in designing and delivering complete data warehouse solutions tailored to your business needs. Whether you are starting from scratch or looking to improve your current infrastructure, our team has the expertise to support you at every stage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are experienced with both Microsoft SQL Server and Oracle platforms, allowing us to align our solutions with your existing environment or recommend the most suitable technology stack for your goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporting &amp; BI</title>
      <link>https://jirimar.github.io/products/reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jirimar.github.io/products/reporting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EN - Reporting (TBD)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT support</title>
      <link>https://jirimar.github.io/products/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jirimar.github.io/products/support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EN IT Support deatil (TBD)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>https://jirimar.github.io/products/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jirimar.github.io/products/consulting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We provide expert IT consulting services tailored to meet the specific needs of your business. Our consultants bring nearly 20 years of hands-on experience in software development, covering a wide range of technologies, architectures, and project environments. We assist clients in areas such as system design, software architecture, process optimization, and technology selection. Whether you are planning a new system, modernizing legacy applications, or addressing specific technical challenges, our team offers deep industry knowledge and practical guidance to support successful project outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
